mojovox.com 2011-10-05

# MojoVox: Privacy Policy

> Mojovox.com ("Mojovox") has created this Privacy Policy to explain our information-gathering and dissemination practices. Your use of our site confirms your acknowledgement and acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy to comply with applicable laws, to improve your Mojovox experience, or to reflect any general change in our policy. Any changes will be posted to this document so that you will always know what information we gather and how we use it. You are encouraged to print or download a copy of this document for your permanent records. We can be reached by email at support@mojovox.com, by postal mail at 901 Mariners Island Blvd., Suite 105, San Mateo, CA 94404, USA, or by telephone at (650) 209-6490. Please let us know of any possible violation of these policies. 

> ## What information does Mojovox collect?

> ### Personally Identifiable Information

We only obtain and retain personally identifiable information that you give to us and certain related transactional information which we collect based on your use of our sites. For example, you might supply your email address by contacting us. You also may supply personally identifiable information, including your name, email address, and location by submitting questions or comments to our various public forums.   
We may collect information concerning the transaction activities of users of our sites when they access different areas of our site. This transaction information includes information about the portions of our site such users visit and information about what data they access. 

> ### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

When you visit the public parts of our sites, we do not collect data about who you are or any other personally identifiable information except as described above. We do, however, collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you based upon your activity on our site. We may collect machine data such as processor type, processor speed, operating system type, browser type, audio devices, modem devices, and video cards. This information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. 

> ### Cookies

Cookies are small data files that are sent from our servers to your computer during a browsing session. In order to make our site more responsive to the needs of our visitors, we may use cookies to assign your Internet browser a unique random number, a sort of anonymous user ID that is stored in a file on your computer. By using a cookie, we are able to automatically identify your browser and track your use of our site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies by default, but contain an option for you to turn off the acceptance of cookies if you prefer. You can also delete cookie files from your computer after they have been stored. 

> ### Children's Information

In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and fair information practices, MojoVox does not intentionally collect any personally identifiable information from children. 

> ## How does Mojovox use the information we collect?

### Personally Identifiable Information

Other than information you supply on our forums or other discussion areas and as described in the next three paragraphs, we do not sell, rent, loan, or otherwise share personally identifiable information, including email lists, to third parties. You need not take any action to prevent such disclosure.   
We may share all of the kinds of nonpublic personal information we collect with: 

  * Third Parties 
    * In connection with, or as may be necessary to service or process a product or service requested or authorized by you, or to effect, administer, or enforce a transaction requested or authorized by you. 
    * Service providers, including those providing marketing services (such as mailing, events management, marketing analysis, and similar services), compliance services, accounting, institutional brokerage services, transaction processing, and systems support. 
    * Third parties may include data processing companies, compliance support organizations, and marketing organizations. 
  * Affiliates 
    * We may provide all of the nonpublic personal information we collect about you to our affiliates to enable them or enhance our ability to offer you new or additional products or services, improve the quality of the products and services we currently offer to you, and to aid us and them in the assessment of our existing products and services and the development of new products or services. 
    * Affiliates may include providers of systems support and services, and compliance services. 

We may be required by law, court order, governmental agency, or law enforcement authority to disclose your personally identifiable information. We may also disclose your information to law enforcement authorities investigating suspected illegal activity. We do not combine personally identifiable information with any of the non-personally identifiable information gathered on the public portions of our sites. 

> ## Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We compile and analyze non-personally identifiable information on an aggregated basis. But because we do not know their names or addresses, they are anonymous to us. We may also use this information to conduct internal research on our visitors' demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand and serve our visitors. 

> ## How do I change my information?

To change or remove any personally identifiable information you have submitted to us, please contact us at support@mojovox.com. 

> ## What levels of security does Mojovox have?

The public portions of our site are not encrypted or password-protected. We do use industry-standard security measures to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. However, due to the inherent dangers of the Internet, we cannot guarantee the protection of such information against interception, misappropriation, misuse, or alteration. 

>
